Good morning, guys
早上好家伙
Uh, Lele hasn't been feeling so well, but I think she'll be better today. So let's wake her up.
嗯，乐乐感觉不太好，但我想她今天会好起来的。让我们叫醒她。
Good morning, baby
宝贝早安
How are you?
你好吗？
Pffffftftftftftftff (cough)
Pffffftftftftftftff（咳嗽）
Sorry, I'm just feeling pregnant
对不起，我只是怀孕了
(gasp) It's okay, baby (gasp)
没关系，宝贝
Y-y-you have-you have-you have something your-(smack) shut your-
是的-你有-你有-你的东西-（快餐）关闭你的-
Close your eyes, close your eyes
闭上你的眼睛，闭上你的眼睛
Ok, ok, ok, ok, ok
好吧好吧好吧好吧
Oof, I'm excited
哎呀，我很兴奋
And... open!
还有...打开！
(gasp) Ooooooooooh my god!
（天哪）噢，天哪！
(screeches)
（尖叫声）
Why is it pink?
为什么是粉红色？
Because we're gonna have a girl
因为我们要有一个女孩
We don't know that
我们不知道
Excuse me, señora
对不起，塞诺拉
(speaks spanish)
（讲西班牙语）
Wait, w-who's that?
等等，那是谁？
T-thats the baby's-babysitter
T-多数民众赞成在婴儿的保姆
Excuse me, señora
对不起，塞诺拉
The baby's not even here yet
婴儿还没来
One second one second.
一秒一秒。
Maybe-maybe we just go into the other room
也许-也许我们只是进入另一个房间
Shhhhhhhhhhhh!
Shhhhhhhhhhh！
(speaks spanish)
（讲西班牙语）
What does that mean?
这意味着什么？
She loves you, anyways...
反正她爱你
I need the receipts for this
我需要收据
No
没有
Excuse me, señora
对不起，塞诺拉
Can we maybe speak privately, without Consuelos?
我们可以在没有Consuelos的情况下私​​下讲话吗？
Consuelos is part of the family right now, ok?
Consuelos现在是一家人了，好吗？
(speaks spanish)
（讲西班牙语）
(cough) Ok
（咳嗽）好
Ok, so we're gonna invite Strode to the gender-reveal party
好吧，我们要邀请Strode参加性别揭露派对
(hoot) Let's do it
（呼呼）做吧
Let's do it! Ok, ok ready?
我们开始做吧！好吧好吧
Surprise her, surprise her
给她一个惊喜，给她一个惊喜
Ok, ready?
准备好了？
You're invited to the-
邀请您参加-
(gasp)
（喘气）
Excuse me, señora
对不起，塞诺拉
(disgusted noise)
（恶心的声音）
Ok, well let's give them some space
好吧，让我们给他们一些空间
¡¿Que?! Space?! No no no no this is my house!
Q ?!空间？！不，不，不，这是我的房子！
(speaks spanish)
（讲西班牙语）
My love, they're never working there, they never clean anything!
我的爱人，他们从不在那里工作，他们从不清理任何东西！
So sorry, so sorry
对不起对不起
This is a-
这是一个-
(demonic noises)
（恶魔般的声音）
Ok, lets go! Ok, lets go! Hurry up!
好了，走吧！好了，走吧！赶快！
Lets go!
我们走吧！
Woo!
！
Ey!
y！
(clapping)
（拍手）
We have no idea its a girl. No idea
我们不知道它是一个女孩。不知道
It is a girl
是一个女孩
Like, I know its going to be a girl!
就像，我知道它将要成为女孩！
(chattering)
（ch不休）
I don't even know, I-I-
我什至不知道，II-
Twan! Twan! I know he's pretty exited-Twan, come here, meet the girls, meet the girls Twa-TWAN!
wan！ wan！我知道他很漂亮-Twan，来这里，认识女孩，认识女孩Twa-TWAN！
Kisses! Oh my god, Strode, Strode, Strode look, look, Consuelo, Consuelo has something to tell you
吻！哦，我的天哪，斯特罗德，斯特罗德，斯特罗德的样子，瞧，孔苏埃洛，孔苏埃洛有话要告诉你
Amor, this is my son, now your son
阿莫尔，这是我儿子，现在是你儿子
(gasp) ¡¿Papa?!
（g）爸爸？！
Strode? Strode?
大步走？大步走？
Hey, uh, no?
嘿，不是吗？
¡Papa! ¡Papa! ¡Papa!
爸爸！爸爸！爸爸！
No!
没有！
(mumbling and crying)
（喃喃自语和哭泣）
No, it's your family!
不，是你的家人！
It's your family, Strode!
是你的家人，斯特罗德！
(speaks spanish)
（讲西班牙语）
Ok, so Strode left and now I'm taking care of the camera now
好吧，Strode离开了，现在我要照顾摄像机
Sweetie!
亲爱的！
I hate my life so much, guys
各位，我非常讨厌我的生活
What?
什么？
(cough) No baby, I-I love my life, right guys?
（咳嗽）没有孩子，我爱我一生，对吗？
Yeah! Yeah, yeah
是的是啊
Cheers! To ever, right?
干杯!到永远吧？
Ok
好
Yo, you got a boyfriend or shomething
哟，你有男朋友或穿鞋
What?
什么？
Twan!
wan！
(chattering)
（ch不休）
TWAN!
TWAN！
What?! I'm not doing nothing!
什么？！我什么也没做！
I'll be right back!
我马上回来！
(grunts)
（咕gr声）
Strode?!
大步走？！
Strode!
大步前进！
Stro-
斯特罗
Strode get down from there!
大步从那里下来！
No!
没有！
Get down-get-get down before!-
快点下来吧！-
Don't make me-don't make me
不要让我-不要让我
(earRAPE)
（earRAPE）
Ay
y
Hey guys, so this is Dr. Wan and he's has the gender review
大家好，我是万博士，他接受了性别审核
Ok, everybody for a little countdown?
好吧，大家都倒计时了吗？
YadeeYAAAAA (yelling) Woo!
YadeeYAAAAA（大喊）呜！
Let's do it!
我们开始做吧！
3, 2, 1
3 2 1
(yelling) WAA!
（大喊）WAA！
We're having a boy! We're having a boy!
我们有一个男孩！我们有一个男孩！
WE'RE HAVING A BOY!
我们有一个男孩！
(cheering)
（欢呼）
Yeah, and I got one more thing to tell ya...
是的，我还有一件事要告诉你...
Uh, youre having twins
呃，你有双胞胎
Is one of them a girl?!
其中一个是女孩吗？
No, its a boy...
不，是个男孩
(screaming and yelling)
（大喊大叫）
BOYS! BOYS! WERE HAVING BOYS!
男孩！男孩！有男孩！
2 boys everyone!
每个人都有2个男孩！
(screaming and yelling)
（大喊大叫）
You know what?! I'm going to take a break from you and the kids!
你知道吗？！我要和你和孩子们休息一下！
You cannot do that!
你不能这样做！
Why not?!
为什么不？！
Because they're in your stomach!
因为它们在你的肚子里！
Ok, well I'm breaking up with you!
好吧，我要和你分手！
No n-listen you cannot break up with me!
不听，你不能和我分手！
WHY?!?!?!?!?!?
为什么？！？！？！？！？！？
Because im marring you
因为我在伤害你
Please...
请...